Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops,
listening to the evening breeze♪
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪Years of companionship
vanish like mist♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪The returned soul
wears robes of regret♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪Into a story♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=Episode 2=
This is a Mobei assassin group's totem.
What's your connection to Mobei?
What are you scheming?
I happened to see it.
Just curious about it.
Are you trying to police my curiosity?
If you keep lying,
I'll have to kick you out of my mansion.
What totem did you mention earlier?
I've never seen it.
Why don't you draw it for me?
Mu Yunqing.
Let go of me!
We've not consummated our marriage yet.
I can still send you back home in time.
Or I can divorce you right now.
Choose one.
Two options.
What if I reject both?
What scheme brings you here?
My scheme is about you.
I covet your beauty.
I cherish your tenderness.
I even fantasize about your love.
I'm warning you.
If you plot anything,
don't blame me for turning ruthless.
Childhood sweethearts?
It's all lies!
I'll stubbornly stay in this mansion,
making you loathe me day and night,
yet unable to drive me away.
Bring me the good wine.
It's run out.
You drank it all.
If you don't fetch it,
I'll get it myself.
My lady.
My lady!
Calm down!
Calm down.
I'm not calm!
Maybe I should just jump down here.
This life is unbearable!
I might as well jump...
Let me just jump and end it.
I was already at the gate...
Listen to me.
He's at the Flower House.
Flower House?
Help me up.
Where's the Flower House?
The eastern part of the city.
There?
Go.
(Flower House)
It's getting late.
A night like this
is too precious to waste.
Why not do something interesting
to spend it?
I've heard many Mobei merchants
enjoy listening
to your Ballad of the Desert.
Are you from Mobei as well?
You must be kidding.
Someone of my status
needs unique talents
to make those Mobei merchants
spend willingly on me.
Didn't you also spend
extravagantly for me,
my lord?
Miss Luo,
(Holding Wine Against the Wind)
if you remember my generosity,
refuse those Mobei merchants
and accompany only me from now on.
The night is long.
Let's go to bed early.
(Continuing will alert her.)
(Better retreat for now.)
No need.
I should leave.
(City Lord's Mansion)
Catch me! Here!
I'm here!
Here!
I caught you!
This way!
Madam, here!
I caught...
I caught you!
What?
Who allowed you to...?
Are you satisfied?
Who...?
Yu Yingwan,
what's with your taste?
All of you, get out!
My taste?
Look at yourself and you'll understand.
Disgraceful!
Yu Yingwan,
do you realize what you're doing?
If you can visit the Flower House,
I can have fun too.
(Breeze, Cloud)
I'll find my own fun.
Let me go.
Yunqing.
Am I dreaming?
Is it only in dreams
that you wouldn't bully me,
wouldn't divorce me,
wouldn't abandon me?
Yunqing.
You never know
how happy I am to see you again.
Don't leave me again, okay?
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
Wan.
Do you know
I didn't want to either?
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪
About last night...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
You're absolutely terrible.
No! Last night,
you were the one who started it.
Then I...
Still gesturing about it?
I drank too much.
Why didn't you push me away?
Because...
I...
Because what?
What?
If you can't explain it,
let's go ask Grandfather to judge!
No! Don't go!
(This scent)
(feels familiar.)
(This is incense from Mobei.)
You visited the Flower House last night?
Mu Yunqing, you scoundrel!
After what happened
between us last night,
you're asking about that courtesan?
That's not what I meant.
I mean,
you approached Luo Shishi last night?
What's your connection to Mobei?
You...
(Even if Luo Shishi has Mobei patrons,)
(she couldn't get the Yunluo Incense
which costs a fortune.)
(If it truly is the incense,)
(the one colluding with her)
(must be a Mobei dignitary.)
(Since we're fated
to remain husband and wife,)
(I must protect Wan.)
♪Winter snow waltzes
before the courtyard♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You seem so distant,
yet right before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪